BMToonShader Operating Instructions

This time Thank you for your purchase of BMToonShader!
Below we will describe the detailed explanation of each adjustment item.


· Rendering Mode
It will specify the material drawing mode. Each…
-Opaque
Opacity

-Cutout
Mode you do not draw a certain following of alpha value
This mode only, Cutoff parameters are displayed, you can adjust the alpha value to cut.

-Fade
Translucent

-Add
Additive synthesis

It becomes.

--- MainColorParameter

· MainTex
It specifies the texture you want to use to diffuse color of the place referred to in the other shader.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· MainColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of MainTex, it can be adjusted.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

--- ShadowColorParameter

· ShadowTex
It specifies the texture you want to use in "the shadow of the color".
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· ShadowColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of ShadowTex, it can be adjusted.

· ShadowPower
If this parameter to 1 or more, and then multiply the result of the self-multiplied by the main color in the shade of color.
The formula ShadowCol * = pow (MainCol, _ShadowPower); will be.

--- TIPS ---
If you want to set the shadow color for the time being good condition,
Specify the same texture as the MainTex to ShadowTex,
The ShadowColor to white,
Please try to 2.0 ShadowPower. In many cases it will it Ppoku.
----------

--- RampParameter

· RampTex
Specify a one-dimensional texture to adjust the Thun condition
In the initial state,

-katturi
Shadow representation of the so-called Toon shader specific one-step

-katturi2
2 stage shading representation of

-im2
Shade expression was referring to the shader of the phrase popular idol game

-soft
Soft shadow representations of stepless

There has been shipped.
When you own, please do not forget to Wrap Mode of the added texture to the "Clamp" on Unity.

--- ShadowRateParameter

· ShadowRate
We will adjust the "ease becomes the shadow" of the material.

· ShadowRateTex
You can be specified in the texture ShadowRate.
Partially you want to shadow, that is to divide painted the you do not want place death, is possible to realize a more sophisticated shade expression.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: gray

In addition, HighlightRate below are also refer to this texture,
Is the red component of texture Ease become a shadow, the green component is supported to ease becomes a highlight.
(R: 0.5, G: 0.5 is the initial value)

--- HighlightParameter

· HighlightTex
The color of the highlights I can be specified in the texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· HighlightColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of HighlightTex, it can be adjusted.

· HighlightRate
It will specify the ease becomes a highlight.
In addition, it is affected by the green component, transparency of RampTex of the above-mentioned ShadowRateTex.

--- SpecularParameter

· SpecularTex
The color of the specular I can be specified in the texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· SpecularColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of SpecularTex, it can be adjusted.

· SpecularPower
We will adjust the sharpness of the specular.

--- SphereMapParameter

· SphereTex
You can specify the sphere texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: black

· SphereColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of SphereTex, it can be adjusted.

Hair for hair, Hair2
Metal for the iron material is shipped.

· SphereMode
You can choose a method for synthesizing the above-mentioned sphere color.
Added by 0, it does multiplied by 1.

--- EdgeParameter

· EdgeColTex
The edge color I can be specified in the texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· EdgeColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of EdgeColTex, it can be adjusted.

· EdgeSizeTex
The magnitude of the edge I can be specified in the texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· EdgeSize
You can adjust the size of the edge.

--- NormalMapParameter

· NormalMap
You can specify the normal map texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: Bump initial color

· NormalScale
You can adjust the normal map of handed condition.

--- RimLightParameter

· RimLightTex
The color of the rim light you can be specified in the texture.
Texture is not set at the time of the initial value: white

· RimLightColor
The superimposed colors in multiplication for the color of RimLightTex, it can be adjusted.

· RimRampTex
Specify a one-dimensional texture to adjust the depth of the rim light.

· RimLightPower
It is possible to adjust the sharpness of the rim light.

· LightInfluence_Rim
Rim light main lights and synchronize, rim light is weak in order light, will be strong enough become retrograde.


---

Trouble, such as until here demand!
twitter:BeamManP